{
    "subject": "resource/Gauhati_University",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Universities_and_colleges_in_Assam",
    "human_readable": "Gauhati University is about universities and colleges in Assam.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7613033056259155,
            "question": "What type of institutions does Gauhati University relate to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7569032907485962,
            "question": "Does Gauhati University have any affiliated colleges?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.73907071352005,
            "question": "What are some notable programs offered by Gauhati University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7272035479545593,
            "question": "What is the main campus of Gauhati University like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6828495860099792,
            "question": "Is Gauhati University a public or private institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6586430072784424,
            "question": "What are some student organizations or clubs at Gauhati University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6413648128509521,
            "question": "Where is Gauhati University located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5857098698616028,
            "question": "When was Gauhati University established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48196884989738464,
            "question": "Does Gauhati University offer online or distance learning programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43316733837127686,
            "question": "Which state in India is associated with Gauhati University?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gauhati University is about universities and colleges in Assam.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2425_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Gauhati University offer online or distance learning programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2425_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Gauhati University established?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2425_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Gauhati University located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2425_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2425_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about Gauhati University, including its location, affiliated colleges, established year, and the various programs it offers. This clearly indicates that the university is indeed related to universities and colleges in Assam, supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}